PERSONAL

Experienced digital business manager with over four years of experience in the Berlin start-up scene. Looking to start as a fullstack developer, to develop and implement products and not to just create strategy. Excellent reputation in planning and operational improvements. Adaptive and results-oriented with strong networking skills.

SKILLS

- Ruby On Rails
- APIs, JSON, Scraping
- Relational Databases, SQL, Postgres -HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- ES6 Javascript
- Wireframes, Prototyping, UI Design
- Test Driven Development
- Git, Github, Technical Workflow
- Salesforce, Hubspot
- Business Development
- Operations

WORK EXPERIENCE & PROJECTS

MOZUBI.APP

A learning platform for German apprentices with a library, flashcards and exam simulation.

FLOAT YOUR GOAT

An Airbnb clone where you can rent and rent out goats for parties and special moments

DIGITAL BUSINESS CONSULTANT CRTN Marketing GmbH, Berlin

BizDev for Volkswagen, social media strategy for Nolte Bier January 2019 - July 2019

PROGRAMME FEED MANAGER & EDITOR

Microsoft News NL/Wundermedia, Berlin

- Technical support for NewsML, XML, JSON and ATOM feeds. Facilitating the on-boarding of new partners using Microsoft-created tools
- Point of Contact Data & Analytics September 2017 - January 2019

OPERATIONS LEAD NETHERLANDS

Rocket Internet SE / Caterwings GmbH, Berlin

Co-responsible for set up entity from scratch. Development and improvement global processes supply side. Implementation of Salesforce (CRM), setup reporting tools and dashboards.

May 2016 - August 2017

CONTACT DETAILS

Phone 0049-17637353867

Mail

annvaningen@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/annemarie-van-ingen/

Github github.com/avaningen

EDUCATION, TRAINING & INTEREST

LE WAGON BERLIN

Fullstack Developer Coding Bootcamp

October 2019 - December 2019

HU UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES UTRECHT

Bachelor Of Arts: Communications Minored in International Business Management at the Budapest Business School in Hungary August 2010 - June 2014

INTERESTS

Descovering local habits during travelling